All right, Ms. Jensen, before we begin,
may I offer you a refreshment?
Water, coffee, tea?
(Sheldon:)A marijuana cigarette?
(Ms Jenson:)No, thanks, I'm fine.
(Sheldon:)Are you sure?
Everyone's smoking them.
(Sheldon:)I think they're the best.
- I don't do drugs.
- Excellent.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. That was a ruse.
(Sheldon:)They're not the best. Physics is the best.
(Sheldon:)By the way, coffee was also
an unacceptable choice.
(Sheldon:)All right, so I see here
you're from Des Moines, Iowa.
(Sheldon:)You're summa cum laude in theoretical
physics from Stanford University.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and two years ago
you had a persistent ear infection.
(Sheldon:)I hope that didn't cause
any hearing loss.
(Ms Jenson:)No, of course not.
(Ms Jenson:)How did you know about that?
Well, I did a comprehensive
background check.
(Sheldon:)Medical records, credit reports,
criminal history.